<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Juby Varughese</title><link>https://juby-gif.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Juby Varughese</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><managingEditor>juby@bcinnovationlabs.com (Juby Varughese)</managingEditor><webMaster>juby@bcinnovationlabs.com (Juby Varughese)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 12:52:36 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://juby-gif.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Interconnection of Electrical Equipments using Wireless Power Transmission</title><link>https://juby-gif.github.io/posts/wireless-power-transmission/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 12:52:36 +0600</pubDate><author>juby@bcinnovationlabs.com (Juby Varughese)</author><guid>https://juby-gif.github.io/posts/wireless-power-transmission/</guid><description>This was a mini project that I&amp;rsquo;ve done during my Engineering at University. We developed an idea that uses Wireless Power Transmission Technology for charging electrical appliances. The problem we were facing during the initial stage was the limited power access for the appliances. For example, to charge our mobile phones we have to have a charger with us everytime and even though we had one, still we could connect only one at a time.</description></item><item><title>Artificial Intelligence on Health care</title><link>https://juby-gif.github.io/posts/artificial-intelligence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 12:52:36 +0600</pubDate><author>juby@bcinnovationlabs.com (Juby Varughese)</author><guid>https://juby-gif.github.io/posts/artificial-intelligence/</guid><description>Well, before jumping into the actual topic we should understand what an AI is and we&amp;rsquo;re going to see that next.
What is Artificial Intelligence ? Artificial Intelligence is the technology that is developed on stimulating human intelligence on smart machines or robots which are programmatically capable of replicating human actions and interactions. Ideally, it is based on the principle that human intelligence can be defined in a way that a machine can easily adapt, replicate it and execute tasks, from the most simple to those that are even more complex.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://juby-gif.github.io/page/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>juby@bcinnovationlabs.com (Juby Varughese)</author><guid>https://juby-gif.github.io/page/about/</guid><description>Who am I? Full Stack Developer, I develop web-apps using the Agile methodology and I am exact in research that I do, to validate customer needs to ensure I am building a product feature that solves a customer pain. This attention to detail, and to my customer’s needs, creates a user experience that puts the customer first. It is important to me, to build products, that help people, and are focused on solving bigger societal issues.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://juby-gif.github.io/page/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>juby@bcinnovationlabs.com (Juby Varughese)</author><guid>https://juby-gif.github.io/page/projects/</guid><description>The Projects i have done for companies:
INNOVATION SPACE
I was the Team Leader on a project that developed a digital community portal for the early stage entrepreneurs for BCI Innovation labs, a local non-profit education provider.
CANADIAN TALENT ACCELERATOR
I developed a Job Portal to attract International tech talent professionals to Canada for IIAD Global. The portal has an employment form, single sign on with LinkedIn and Google, employees can put up the new job posting, and candidates have their space to get registered and look for jobs with different searching parameters.</description></item><item><title>References</title><link>https://juby-gif.github.io/page/references/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>juby@bcinnovationlabs.com (Juby Varughese)</author><guid>https://juby-gif.github.io/page/references/</guid><description>I have hired Juby as a contract full-stack developer for number of my projects and the results have been spectacular!
The first line of work involved writing a prototype frontend web-app using React.js. He accomplished it in a short amount of time with a high quality fully responsive build. When our team presented Juby&amp;rsquo;s work to the client, the client became very pleased. He demonstrated understanding for HTML, CSS, React.</description></item></channel></rss>