<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Juby Varughese</title><link>https://juby-gif.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Juby Varughese</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><managingEditor>juby@bcinnovationlabs.com (Juby Varughese)</managingEditor><webMaster>juby@bcinnovationlabs.com (Juby Varughese)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 12:52:36 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://juby-gif.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Interconnection of Electrical Equipments using Wireless Power Transmission</title><link>https://juby-gif.github.io/posts/wireless-power-transmission/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 12:52:36 +0600</pubDate><author>juby@bcinnovationlabs.com (Juby Varughese)</author><guid>https://juby-gif.github.io/posts/wireless-power-transmission/</guid><description>This was a mini project that I&amp;rsquo;ve done during my Engineering at University. We developed an idea that uses Wireless Power Transmission Technology for charging electrical appliances. The problem we were facing during the initial stage was the limited power access for the appliances. For example, to charge our mobile phones we have to have a charger with us everytime and even though we had one, still we could connect only one at a time.</description></item><item><title>Artificial Intelligence on Health care</title><link>https://juby-gif.github.io/posts/artificial-intelligence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 12:52:36 +0600</pubDate><author>juby@bcinnovationlabs.com (Juby Varughese)</author><guid>https://juby-gif.github.io/posts/artificial-intelligence/</guid><description>Well, before jumping into the actual topic we should understand what an AI is and we&amp;rsquo;re going to see that next.
What is Artificial Intelligence ? Artificial Intelligence is the technology that is developed on stimulating human intelligence on smart machines or robots which are programmatically capable of replicating human actions and interactions. Ideally, it is based on the principle that human intelligence can be defined in a way that a machine can easily adapt, replicate it and execute tasks, from the most simple to those that are even more complex.</description></item></channel></rss>